PREVIOUSLY ON "FRIENDS"...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WON'T BE THERE.
WHY NOT TAKE
TWO DAYS OFF?
BECAUSE I CAN'T, ROSS.
THIS IS MY WEDDING.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHERE YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
IT'S THE MOST BEAUTIFUL PLACE.
IT'S RIGHT OVER...
OH, MY GOD!
POSTPONING IT IS NOT AN OPTION.
THIS WEDDING WON'T HAPPEN.
IF YOU DON'T LOVE THIS
WE'LL DO IT ANY OTHER
PLACE, ANY OTHER TIME.
REALLY, IT'S FINE.
IT'S PERFECT.
I'M GOING TO LONDON.
WHAT?!
IT'S NOT OVER
UNTIL SOMEONE SAYS "I DO."
I DO!
I DO, I DO!
RACHEL, NO!
( phone ringing )
THE WALTHAM RESIDENCE.
HI. IS THIS
EMILY'S PARENTS HOUSE?
This is the housekeeper
speaking.
BY THE WAY, YOUNG LADY
THAT IS NOT HOW ONE
ADDRESSES A PERSON
ON THE TELEPHONE.
First, one identifies oneself
AND THEN ASKS FOR THE PERSON
WITH WHOM ONE WISHES TO SPEAK.
( British accent ):
THIS IS PHOEBE BUFFAY.
I WAS WONDERING, PLEASE
IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE,
PLEASE
MIGHT I SPEAK WITH
MISS EMILY WALTHAM, PLEASE?
MISS WALTHAM
IS AT THE REHEARSAL DINNER
AND IT IS NOT POLITE
TO MAKE FUN OF PEOPLE.
GOOD-BYE.
I'LL BE NICE, I SWEAR.
JUST GIVE ME THE NUMBER
FOR WHERE THEY ARE.
I'M AFRAID I'M NOT AT LIBERTY
TO DIVULGE THAT INFORMATION.
SOMEBODY IS ON THEIR WAY
TO RUIN THE WEDDING.
I HAVE TO WARN SOMEBODY.
SO IF YOU DON'T
GIVE ME THAT NUMBER
I'LL COME OVER THERE
AND KICK YOUR SNOOTY ASS
ALL THE WAY TO
NEW... GLOUCKENSHIRE.
HELLO?
HELLO?!
OOH, SHE KNEW
I COULD KICK HER ASS.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY. HI...
SWEETHEART.
MOM... DAD...
OH, SORRY
WE'RE LATE.
MY FAULT. I INSISTED
ON RIDING THE TUBE.
JUDY, THE KIDS.
JACK, THAT'S WHAT
THEY CALL THE SUBWAY.
OH. I THOUGHT...
DAD, DAD, WE GOT IT,
WE GOT IT.
OH, HERE COMES MY
DAD AND STEPMOM.
MR. AND MRS.
GELLER...
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
THIS IS STEVEN...
AND ANDREA WALTHAM.
HOW DO YOU DO?
VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
DARLING, THE GELLERS.
DARLING, IT'S
THE GELLERS.
SHE'S VERY SELF-
INVOLVED, YOU KNOW.
I SHOULD NEVER
HAVE MARRIED HER.
SORRY, WHAT?
IT'S THE GELLERS.
WHERE?
WELL, THAT'S ONE
AND THERE'S
ANOTHER ONE.
LOVELY TO MEET YOU.
TERRIBLY NICE OF YOU
TO PAY FOR HALF
THE WEDDING.
THE HELL WITH TRADITION.
WE'RE HAPPY TO DO IT.
WE KNOW HOW EXPENSIVE
WEDDINGS CAN BE.
BESIDES, THIS
MAY BE THE ONLY WEDDING
WE GET TO THROW.
A JOKE THAT'S FUNNY
IN ALL COUNTRIES.
SIR?
WHAT'S IN IT?
GOAT CHEESE,
WATERCRESS AND PANCETTA.
THAT'S NOT FOOD.
NO, I DON'T, NO...
EVERYTHING'S DIFFERENT HERE.
I WANT TO GO HOME.
I-I... MISS MY FAMILY.
I MISS THE COFFEEHOUSE.
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER
WHAT PHOEBE LOOKS LIKE.
JOEY, IT'S BEEN
THREE DAYS.
OKAY, YOU'RE JUST...
JUST A LITTLE HOMESICK.
OKAY, WOULD YOU JUST
TRY TO RELAX AND JUST...
JUST ENJOY YOURSELF.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT HERE, TOO.
YOU'RE MEAN IN ENGLAND.
WHAT THE HELL!
WHAT'S UP, DAD?
THIS BILL FOR MY
HALF OF THE WEDDING.
IT'S INSANE.
HOW CAN IT BE
SO MUCH?
THE RECEPTION'S
AT THEIR HOUSE.
FLOWERS, LIQUOR,
RECARPET FIRST FLOOR.
NEW GUEST BATH.
LANDSCAPING.
I'M PAYING TO REMODEL
THIS GUY'S HOUSE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE
THAT SON OF A BITCH
A PIECE OF MY MIND.
DAD.
COME ON. PLEASE
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING
TO UPSET EMILY TONIGHT.
SHE'S HAD A HARD ENOUGH
COUPLE OF DAYS AS IT IS.
HERE. HERE. LET ME
GO TALK TO HIM, OKAY?
WELL, YOU TELL THEM
NO ONE TAKES ADVANTAGE
OF THE GELLERS.
OOH, JACK.
SOMETIMES I FORGET HOW
POWERFUL YOU CAN BE.
AND I'M GOING TO GO GET DRUNK.
OOH, OOH, OOH!
HI.
HELLO.
UM, WHEN IS YOUR NEXT
FLIGHT TO LONDON?
THERE'S ONE LEAVING
IN 30 MINUTES
AND I DO HAVE ONE SEAT LEFT.
OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THE LAST-MINUTE FARE
ON THIS TICKET IS $2,700.
OH. I JUST
DON'T THINK
I HAVE ENOUGH LEFT
ON MY CREDIT CARD.
WELL, YOU CAN SPLIT IT
WITH ANOTHER CREDIT CARD.
WELL, OKAY,
HOW ABOUT FIVE?
OH, THANK YOU.
I'M JUST GOING TO NEED
TO SEE YOUR PASSPORT.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T HAVE IT
BUT I CAN TELL YOU
EXACTLY WHERE IT IS
ON MY NIGHTSTAND
AND... OKAY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
OKAY, I HAVE MY...
I HAVE MY DRIVER'S LICENSE
AND I HAVE A 20.
LOOK, FACE IT: MY FATHER
IS NOT GOING TO PAY
FOR THE BUILT-IN BARBECUE
AND BELIEVE ME, YOU CAN
KISS YOUR GAZEBO GOOD-BYE.
NOW, I MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET YOU THE NEW LAWN.
AH, THEN YOU HAVE TO GIVE US
THE LAWN ORNAMENTS.
I GO BACK THERE
WITH LAWN ORNAMENTS
HE'S GOING TO LAUGH IN MY FACE.
WILL YOU SAY
SOMETHING, STEVEN?!
PLEASE.
DON'T TAKE THAT
TONE WITH ME.
ALL-ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN.
HI, PHEEBS.
OH, THANK GOD,
YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND.
YOU PROBABLY WANT TO BE ALONE
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW I THINK
YOU'RE DOING THE RIGHT THING.
BYE, PHEEBS!
WAIT, WHERE
ARE YOU GOING?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO! WAIT!
GOD! WHY AM I ALWAYS PREGNANT
WHEN SHE DOES THAT?!
I'D LIKE
TO TOAST ROSS AND EMILY.
OF COURSE,
MY BIG TOAST
WILL BE TOMORROW
AT THE WEDDING
SO THIS IS
KIND OF MY LITTLE TOAST
OR MELBA TOAST,
IF YOU WILL.
OKAY.
I'VE KNOWN ROSS
FOR A LONG TIME.
IN FACT, I KNEW HIM
WHEN HE WAS GOING OUT
WITH HIS FIRST GIRLFRIEND
AND I THOUGHT THINGS
WERE GOING
TO WORK OUT FOR THEM--
UNTIL HE OVERINFLATED HER.
OH, DEAR GOD.
WHAT?
( phone ringing )
HELLO, WALTHAM INTERIORS.
OH, HI. MRS. WALTHAM?
I NEED TO SPEAK
WITH EITHER ONE OF THE BEST MEN
OR ROSS'S SISTER, MONICA.
WHO IS THIS?
OH, I'M PHOEBE BUFFAY.
I'M ONE OF ROSS'S BEST FRIENDS.
IF YOU'RE ONE
OF ROSS'S BEST FRIENDS
WHY AREN'T YOU HERE?
I CAN'T FLY.
I'M HAVING MY BROTHER'S BABIES.
OH.
AM I ON THE RADIO?
NO. UM...
COULD I TALK TO ONE OF THEM?
IT'S VERY, VERY IMPORTANT.
NO, I'M BORED WITH YOU NOW.
I'M GOING TO CUT YOU OFF.
OH!
AND I'M SURE
WE'RE ALL VERY EXCITED
THAT ROSS AND EMILY ARE GETTING
MARRIED AT MONTGOMERY HALL.
TO THINK-- MY FRIEND
GETTING MARRIED IN MONTY HALL.
OH, COME ON. MONTY HALL.
LET'S MAKE A DEAL!
COME ON, YOU PEOPLE!
ALL RIGHT, FORGET IT.
CONGRATULATIONS,
ROSS AND EMILY.
OKAY.
HEY, BEST MAN NUMBER TWO,
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
ALL RIGHT, I'M NOT GOOD
WITH THE JOKES
LIKE CHANDLER HERE.
BOY...
BUT, UH...
I JUST WANT TO SAY
CONGRATULATIONS
TO THE HAPPY COUPLE.
I FIRST MET ROSS
IN THIS COFFEEHOUSE BACK HOME...
HOME... YEAH.
NEW YORK CITY.
WHERE EVERYBODY KNOWS MY NAME.
WELL, ANYWAY...
UH... I LOVE YOU GUYS...
BUT NOT AS MUCH
AS I LOVE AMERICA.
COULD WE PLEASE
GO HOME NOW?
ARE YOU GOING HOME?
I WAS HOPING TO GET
TO KNOW YOU BETTER.
I'M NOT GOING
ANYWHERE, SWEETHEART.
I WAS LAUGHING.
OUT LOUD?
WELL, I DIDN'T WANT EVERYONE
TO THINK I WAS STUPID.
SO HOW YOU DOING?
MY MOTHER'S
DRIVING ME CRAZY.
BUT ROSS IS GETTING
MARRIED. I'M HAPPY.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET
ANYTHING SPOIL THAT.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT ROSS
IS A WONDERFUL YOUNG MAN.
THANKS. WE LIKE HIM.
MY GOD.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN A TEENAGER
WHEN YOU HAD HIM.
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL
I'M PAYING FOR IT.
LOOK, WE'RE DOWN
TO JUST ONE POINT.
COULD WE PLEASE MAYBE JUST
SETTLE IT AFTER THE WEDDING?
ALL RIGHT,
BUT I JUST WANT TO SAY
I'M NOT PAYING
FOR YOUR WINE CELLAR
YOU THIEVING,
WOULD-BE-SPEAKING-GERMAN-IF-IT-
WEREN'T-FOR-US
CHEAP LITTLE MAN.
THE GUY WAS HAMMERED, OKAY?
THERE'S NO WAY YOU LOOK
LIKE ROSS'S MOTHER.
THEN WHY WOULD HE SAY IT?
BECAUSE HE'S CRAZY, OKAY?
HE CAME UP TO ME EARLIER
AND THANKED ME
FOR MY VERY MOVING
PERFORMANCE IN TITANIC.
OH, MY MOTHER'S RIGHT.
I'M NEVER GOING
TO GET MARRIED.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THAT IS...
WHO WOULDN'T WANT YOU?
OH, PLEASE.
I'M A SINGLE MOM
WITH A 30-YEAR-OLD SON.
I'M GETTING MARRIED TODAY!
WHOO-HOO!
MORNING, ROSS.
I'M GETTING
MARRIED-- TODAY!
YEAH, YOU ARE!
WHOO-HOO!
DO YOU THINK
HE KNEW I WAS HERE?
WELL, I'VE-I'VE NEVER DONE
THAT WITH YOU BEFORE.
( chuckling ):
NOPE.
SO, UH, HOW ARE YA?
HOW YA... HOW YA...
YOU OKAY?
YEP, YEP.
YOU?
OH, YES, YES.
UH-HUH.
YOU?
WE DID YOU.
WELL...
I BETTER GET GOING.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY, YEAH.
COULD YOU NOT LOOK?
I DON'T WANT TO LOOK.
( sighing )
( rhythmic tapping )
UH... UH, EXCUSE ME.
YEAH?
IF YOU'RE PLANNING
ON DOING THAT
THROUGHOUT
THE ENTIRE FLIGHT
PLEASE TELL ME NOW,
SO THAT I CAN
TAKE A SEDATIVE.
OR MAYBE SLIP YOU ONE.
SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M, UH...
I'M KIND OF EXCITED.
I'M, UH, I'M GOING TO LONDON
TO, UH, TO TELL THIS GUY
THAT I LOVE HIM.
( phone rings )
HELLO?
HEY! WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN?
HEY! I SPENT THE NIGHT OUT.
I MET THIS CUTE BRIDESMAID.
SHE IS SO...
I don't want
TO HEAR ABOUT HER.
AH, PHEEBS, YOU KNOW YOU'RE
STILL MY NUMBER-ONE GIRL.
NO! NO, WE HAVE
AN EMERGENCY, OKAY?
RACHEL'S COMING TO LONDON.
OH, GREAT!
NO, IT'S NOT GREAT, NO!
SHE'S COMING TO TELL ROSS
THAT SHE LOVES HIM!
BUT... HE LOVES EMILY.
I KNOW THAT!
YOU HAVE TO STOP HER!
She'll ruin the wedding!
OKAY.
SO I'VE DONE MY PART, OKAY?
IT'S YOUR RESPONSIBILITY NOW.
THE BURDEN IS OFF ME, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
SO TELL ME ABOUT THIS GIRL.
HEY, HAVE YOU
SEEN MONICA?
I'M NOT SEEING MONICA.
WHAT?
WE GOT TO FIND HER.
PHOEBE JUST CALLED.
RACHEL'S COMING TO TELL ROSS
SHE LOVES HIM!
OH, MY GOD!
WE GOT TO
FIND MONICA-- KNOW WHERE SHE IS?
NO, OKAY?!
WHAT'S WITH THE THIRD DEGREE?!
WHY DON'T YOU JUST SHINE
A LIGHT IN MY EYES?!
...AND SO THEN I REALIZED
ALL THIS STUFF
THAT I HAD BEEN DOING:
PROPOSING TO JOSHUA
LYING TO ROSS ABOUT WHY
I COULDN'T COME TO THE WEDDING
WAS ALL JUST A WAY OF...
OH! OH! OH!
I'M SORRY.
CAN I INTERRUPT?
YEAH, I JUST WANT
TO SAY THAT YOU...
ARE A HORRIBLE,
HORRIBLE PERSON.
EH, P-P-PARDON ME?
YOU SAY YOU LOVE
THIS MAN
YET YOU'RE ABOUT TO RUIN
THE HAPPIEST DAY OF HIS LIFE.
I'M AFRAID I HAVE TO AGREE
WITH YOUR FRIEND PHEEBS.
THIS IS A... THIS IS A
TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE PLAN.
BUT HE HAS TO KNOW
HOW I FEEL!
BUT WHY?
HE LOVES THIS...
THIS EMILY PERSON.
NO GOOD CAN COME OF THIS.
( gasping softly )
I THINK
YOU'RE WRONG.
OH, NO!
OH, BY THE WAY,
IT SEEMS
TO BE PERFECTLY CLEAR
THAT YOU WERE ON A BREAK.
( gasping )
OH, MY GOD!
IT'S LIKE A FAIRYLAND.
I KNOW.
IT'S HORRIBLE, ISN'T IT?
WELL, I LOVE IT.
I ONLY HOPE MY WEDDING
LOOKS THIS GOOD.
I JUST HOPE...
YOU CAN LET SOME OF THEM
GO BY.
( whispering ):
PSST! MONICA!
WE REALLY NEED TO START
LOOKING OUT FOR RACHEL.
I'LL COVER THE FRONT DOOR.
YOU WATCH THAT BIG HOLE
AT THE BACK OF THE BUILDING
AND I GOT CHANDLER
COVERING ROSS.
WHY WOULD I CARE
WHERE CHANDLER IS?
YOU KNOW, UH...
SOMETIMES I DON'T
EVEN LIKE CHANDLER.
OKAY.
Ross:
I DO.
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT;
IT'S THE SECOND ONE.
REALLY?
HELLO, JOEY.
HEY, FELICITY.
UM, I THOUGHT
ABOUT YOU ALL DAY.
YEAH?
( giggling ):
TALK NEW YORK TO ME AGAIN.
FUGGETABOUTIT...
MMM....
( deep voice):
HOW YOU DOIN'?
MMM!
OH, YEAH...
THERE'S NOTHING TO DISCUSS.
WE'RE NOT PAYING
FOR YOUR WINE CELLAR.
YOU HAVE TO MEET ME
IN THE MIDDLE HERE.
YOU KEEP PUSHING
MY FOOT WILL MEET
YOUR ASS!
Ross:
DAD!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
NOTHING, NOTHING.
EVERYTHING'S UNDER CONTROL.
YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME, SIR?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME?
Ross:
THAT'S IT!
PARENTS! PARENTS! BACK AWAY!
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS OUR
WEDDING DAY!
FROM NOW ON,
EVERYONE GETS ALONG
AND IF I HEAR ONE MORE WORD
NO GRANDCHILDREN.
THAT'S RIGHT!
OKAY, OKAY.
SORRY, OLD BOY,
SORRY.
SORRY, SORRY.
( muttering ):
I COULD KILL YOU
WITH MY THUMB, YOU KNOW.
WHAT WAS
ALL THAT ABOUT?
( sighing ):
IT WAS THIS
DISAGREEMENT OVER...
( sighing )
MY GOD, YOU...
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
OH...
YOU ARE NOT MEANT TO
SEE ME BEFORE THE WEDDING.
IT'S BAD LUCK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK WE'VE HAD
ALL THE BAD LUCK
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE.
OOH...
MY GOD! RACHEL!
( laughing )
YOU'RE HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
WELL, I JUST CAME...
I JUST NEEDED
TO TELL YOU...
CONGRATULATIONS.
( acoustic folk music playing)
( phone ringing )
WALTHAM INTERIORS.
Mrs. Waltham, hi.
It's Phoebe again.
CAN I PLEASE
TALK TO ONE OF THE BEST MEN?
THIS IS THE LAST TIME,
I PROMISE.
JOEY, THERE'S A GIRL
ON THE PHONE FOR YOU.
GREAT!
HELLO.
Joey, it's Phoebe.
DID YOU STOP RACHEL?
It's okay.
SHE JUST CAME AND
GAVE HIM A HUG.
SO, NOTHING GOT RUINED?
No.
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT!
SO, WHAT'S GOING ON NOW?
UH... I'M WALKING
DOWN THE AISLE.
STILL WALKING.
NOW, I'M AT THE
FRONT WITH ROSS.
IT'S PHOEBE.
HE LOOKS PRETTY MAD.
UH... I BETTER GO.
NO, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
HOLD IT UP SO I CAN LISTEN!
WHAT WE DID LAST NIGHT WAS...
STUPID.
TOTALLY CRAZY AND STUPID.
WHAT WERE WE THINKING?
BUT I'M COMING
TO YOUR ROOM TONIGHT, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, DEFINITELY.
( playing
"Here Comes The Bride" )
FRIENDS
FAMILY, WE'RE GATHERED
TO CELEBRATE HERE TODAY
THE JOYOUS UNION
OF ROSS AND EMILY.
MAY THE HAPPINESS
we share with them today
BE WITH THEM ALWAYS.
NOW, EMILY,
REPEAT AFTER ME.
I, EMILY...
TAKE THEE,
ROSS...
TAKE THEE, ROSS...
AS MY LAWFULLY
WEDDED HUSBAND
IN SICKNESS
AND IN HEALTH
TILL DEATH PARTS US.
AS MY LAWFULLY WEDDED HUSBAND
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH
UNTIL DEATH PARTS US.
NOW, ROSS
REPEAT AFTER ME.
I, ROSS...
TAKE THEE, EMILY...
TAKE THEE, RACHEL...
EMILY.
( chuckles nervously )
UH...
SHALL I GO ON?
Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]